Destination Calabria
Destination unknown known known known known
I left my job my boss my car and my home
I'm leavin' for a destination
I still don't know
Somewhere nobody must have beauties at all
And if you like us you can follow me
So let's go follow me and let's go
To the place where we belong and leave our troubles at home
Come with me we can go
To a paradise of love and joy a destination unknown
Now I won't feel those heavy shoulders no more
My life got better now
I finally enjoy
Yes all the people wanna come here and so
Come on and join us you can do that now
Let's go follow me and let's go
To the place where we belong and leave our troubles at home
Come with me we can go
To a paradise of love and joy a destination unknown
Known known known known unknown
Destination unknown
Destination unknown  unknown
Destination unknown follow me and let's go
To the place where we belong and leave our troubles at home
Come with me we can go
To a paradise of love and joy a destination unknown